A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Issue Books, Series 17 FA363
Rockefeller Archive Center
- 1964 Presidential Election, 1959-1964; 1; 9.2 Cubic Feet
  - Volume 19 - Foreign Aid, 1961-1964 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    Tab 31 Platform Planks Revised, Foreign Aid, June 30, 1964
    Tab 32 Proposals of the Critical Issues Council, Foreign Aid, July 2, 1964 -- Kissinger memoranda detailing the proposals of the Republican Citizens Committee's Critical Issues Council.
    Tab 33 NAR Suggestion for Platform Committee, Foreign Aid, July 7, 1964
    Tab 34 Background Material on Proposed Planks, Foreign Aid, July 10, 1964
    Tab 35 Summary of Academic Proposals, Foreign Aid, July 20, 1964 -- contributions and views of the academic community on foreign aid.
  - Volume 20 - Latin America, 1959-1964 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    Tab 1 NAR Statement, Latin America, December 17, 1959 -- Transcript of remarks by NAR delivered at Dallas Council of World Affairs and the Press Club of Dallas Luncheon.
    Tab 2 Background Paper, Nationalism in Latin America, prepared by Arthur Whitaker, January 27, 1960 -- paper written by Professor Whitaker of the Department of History, University of Pennsylvania.
    Tab 3 Background Paper, the Western Hemisphere in a Ten-Year Perspective, prepared by John Plank, February 15, 1960
    Tab 4 Summary Paper, Latin America, June 29, 1960
    Tab 5 NAR Statement, Latin America, July 12, 1960 -- published booklet of NAR speech, delivered at the New York Young Republican Club.
    Tab 6 Comparison of Republican and Democratic Platforms, Latin America, September 9, 1960
    Tab 7 Study Papers, Latin America, November 23, 1960
  - Volume 20 - Latin America, 1959-1964 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    Tab 8 Background Paper, Study of the Latin American Future, May 12, 1961 -- summary of survey of Latin American economic and social development, as it appeared in the London "Economist" of April 22, 1959.
    Tab 9 Background Paper, Latin America - General, September 22, 1961
    Tab 10 Questions and Answers prepared for NAR Television Appearance, Latin America, January 11, 1962
    Tab 11 Position Paper, Appraisal of Punta del Este Conference, February 8, 1962
    Tab 12 Position Paper, Latin America - General, April 12, 1962
    Tab 13 Background Paper, Alliance for Progress: Agrarian Reform, May 1962
    Tab 14 Position Paper, Latin America - General, October 1, 1962
    Tab 15 Current Positions Cards, Latin America, October 25, 1962
    Tab 16 Background Paper, Latin America: Two-Year Summary, January 1963
    Tab 17 Background Paper, Dominican Republic, January 7, 1963 -- Kissinger memoranda with background information on Juan Bosch, President-elect of the Dominican Republic.
    Tab 18 Background Paper, Argentina, January 25, 1963 -- Kissinger memoranda with information in advance of NAR meeting with Argentinean Foreign Minister.
    Tab 19 Background Paper, Venezuela's Position in Relation to U.S. Foreign Policy, February 21, 1963 -- memoranda with information provided by Adolf Berle in advance of NAR meeting with Venezuelan President Betancourt.
    Tab 20 Background Paper, Summaries of Lleras and Kubitschek Reports, July 29, 1963 -- Kissinger memoranda with Ann Black's summary of the Alliance for Progress.
    Tab 21 Background Paper, Summary of "The Wine is Bitter," August 9, 1963 -- Ann Black's analysis of 1953 book by Milton Eisenhower on political conditions in Latin America.
  - Volume 21 - Latin America, 1959-1964 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    Tab 22 Background Paper, Summary of Academic Proposals for Latin American Policy, August 1963
    Tab 23 Questions and Answers for "U.S. News & World Report" Interview, Latin America, September 12, 1963
    Tab 24 Summary of NAR Proposals, Latin America, October 1963
    Tab 25 NAR Statement, Latin America, October 10, 1963 -- published booklet of NAR speech delivered at Western Hemisphere Day Dinner.
  - Volume 21 - Latin America, 1959-1964 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    Tab 26 Position Paper, Latin America - General, December 1963
    Tab 27 Campaign Research Kit, Latin America, January 1, 1964 -- published campaign material with NAR position on Latin America.
    Tab 28 Background Paper, The Crisis in Panama, January 13, 1964 -- suggested NAR position on the Panama Canal.
    Tab 29 Background Paper, The Political Status of Puerto Rico, January 14, 1964 -- suggested NAR position on political issues surrounding Puerto Rico.
    Tab 30 Position Paper, The Panama Crisis, January 15, 1964 -- Kissinger memoranda on the issues surrounding the Panama Canal.
    Tab 31 Background Paper, Chilean Elections, January 21, 1964 -- fact sheet on upcoming Chilean elections [that ultimately brought Salvatore Allende to power].
    Tab 32 Background Paper, Panama: Renegotiating the Treaty and Alleged Text of JFK Commitment, February 18, 1964 -- Kissinger memo regarding disputed agreement reportedly signed between the US and Panama.
    Tab 33 California Republican Assembly Questionnaire, Latin America, February 27, 1964 -- specific questions on Latin America, as proposed by the Republican Assembly.
    Tab 34 Position Paper, Appointment of Assistant Secretary of State Mann, March 1964 -- suggested NAR position on the appointment of Mann to fill a position once held by NAR.
    Tab 35 Position Paper, The Brazilian Crisis, April 2, 1964 -- suggested NAR position on the leftist tendencies of the Brazilian government.
    Tab 36 Draft Background Paper, Article on Latin America for College Paper, April 3, 1964 -- suggested text for NAR article on Latin America for inclusion in college newspapers.
    Tab 37 Background Paper, Panama: Proposals of Critical Issues Council, April 9, 1964 -- Kissinger memoranda detailing the proposals of the Republican Citizens Committee's Critical Issues Council regarding Panama.
    Tab 38 Draft NAR Statement, Latin America, April 16, 1964 -- Kissinger draft speech for NAR on Latin America.
    Tab 39 NAR Statement, Latin America, April 12, 1964 -- press release of speech on Latin America, delivered at the Pan American Press Seminar, New Orleans, Louisiana.
    Tab 40 Fact Sheet, The Crisis in Panama, May 5, 1964
    Tab 41 Kuchel Memorandum Analysis, Latin America, May 11, 1964 -- memoranda highlighting the differences in position between Senator Goldwater and the 1960 Republican Party Platform.
    Tab 42 "As a Republican, I Believe.. ." Latin America, May 11, 1964 -- section pertaining to Latin America from published brochure of NAR positions on issues affecting the United States and the Republican Party.
    Tab 43 Draft Platform Planks, Latin America, May 29, 1964
    Tab 44 Platform Analysis Notebook, Latin America, May 1964
    Tab 45 Platform Planks, Latin America, June 3, 1964
    Tab 46 "Model" Platform Planks, Latin America, June 18, 1964
    Tab 47 NAR Suggestions for the Platform Committee, Latin America, July 7, 1964
  - Volume 22 - Middle East, 1959-1964 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    Tab 1 Background Paper, The Middle East: A Ten-Year Perspective, prepared by J. Badeau, February 23, 1960
    Tab 2 Background Paper, Middle East, prepared by C. Issawi, April 18, 1960
    Tab 3 Position Paper, Middle East, prepared by M. W. Thornburg, June 16, 1960
    Tab 4 Comparison of Republican and Democratic Platforms, Middle East, September 9, 1960
    Tab 5 Background Paper, Iran: Report No. 1, October 27, 1961 -- Kissinger paper on Iran.
  - Volume 22 - Middle East, 1959-1964 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    Tab 6 Questions and Answers for NAR Television Appearance, Middle East, January 11, 1962
    Tab 7 Background Paper, Iran: Report No. 2, February 21, 1962
    Tab 8 Position Paper, Iran, April 16, 1962
    Tab 9 Position Paper, Middle East - General, April 16, 1962
    Tab 10 Background Paper, Iran: Report No. 3, April 23, 1962
    Tab 11 Background Paper, Iran: Report No. 4, June 25, 1962 -- Kissinger memo with additional information on Iran.
    Tab 12 Position Paper, Middle East - General, October 10, 1962
    Tab 13 Background Paper, Afghanistan, September 10, 1963
    Tab 14 Summary of NAR Proposals, Middle East, October 1963 -- NAR proposals on Middle Eastern issues.
    Tab 15 Background Paper, Chronological Study of Yemen: 1960-November 22, 1963, November 23, 1963
    Tab 16 Position Paper, Middle East - General, December 1963
    Tab 17 Background Paper, The Arab-Israeli Dispute, March 10, 1964
    Tab 18 Position Paper, U.S. Policy toward the Arab-Israeli Dispute, April 23, 1964
    Tab 19 Platform Analysis Notebook, Middle East, May 1964
    Tab 20 Fact Sheet, Yemen-Aden Dispute, May 11, 1964 -- proposals outlining US policy toward Yemeni Civil War.
    Tab 21 Draft Platform Planks, Middle East, May 29, 1964
    Tab 22 Platform Planks (Revised), Middle East, June 3, 1964
    Tab 23 Draft Nar Statement, Arabia, June 5, 1964 -- draft of NAR speech on Middle East issues.
    Tab 24 "Model" Platform, Middle East, June 18, 1964
    Tab 25 NAR Suggestions for Platform Committee, Middle East, July 7, 1964
  - Volume 23 - North Atlantic Treaty Organization, 1959-1964 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    Tab 1 Background Paper and Summary, A-2, NATO: Problem of Security and Collaboration, prepared by Robert Osgood, November 6, 1959 -- paper written by Professor Osgood of the University of Chicago.
    Tab 2 Background Paper and Summary, A-3, NATO: General, unattributed, prepared by General Theodore Parker, November 10, 1959
    Tab 3 Background Paper and Summary, A-1, Problems, Opportunities and Immediate Tasks, prepared by Robert Strausz-Hupe, December 1, 1959 -- paper written by Dr. Strausz-Hupe, Chairman of the Foreign Policy Research Institute, University of Pennsylvania.
    Tab 4 Position Paper, A-1, A-2, A-3, Western Europe, May 26, 1960
    Tab 5 Comparison of Republican and Democratic Platforms, September 9, 1960
    Tab 6 Current Positions Cards, October 25, 1960
    Tab 7 Background Paper, Possible Plan for a North Atlantic Confederation, November 15, 1960
  - Volume 23 - North Atlantic Treaty Organization, 1959-1964 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    Tab 8 Background Paper, Study Papers on the North Atlantic Community, December 1960
    Tab 9 Position Paper, Centralized Control Over Nuclear Weapons, February 8, 1962
    Tab 10 Background Paper, NATO: Report No. 1, January 15, 1961, February 15 & 16, 1962
    Tab 11 Position Paper, NATO: General, April 16, 1962
    Tab 12 Position Paper, Western Europe Defense, September 28, 1963
    Tab 13 Background Paper, British Government References to Skybolt Incident, January 3, 1963 -- Kissinger memoranda on the issues regarding US-Great Britain defense initiative.
    Tab 14 NAR Statement, NATO and European Integration, February 9, 1963 -- press release of NAR remarks.
  - Volume 23 - North Atlantic Treaty Organization, 1959-1964 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    Tab 15 NAR Statement, NATO and European Integration, April 25, 1963 -- press release of NAR speech delivered at the Bureau of American Newspaper Publishers Association, Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, New York City.
    Tab 16 Background Paper, Major Issues Facing NATO, July 29, 1963
    Tab 17 Questions and Answers for "U.S. News & World Report," September 5, 1963 -- specific questions on NATO posed to NAR as part of interview with the news magazine.
    Tab 18 Summary of NAR Proposals, NATO, October 1963
    Tab 19 Draft NAR Statement, Troop Withdrawal from Europe, November 1, 1963
    Tab 20 Position Paper, Goldwater Statement on Tactical Nuclear Weapons, October 29, 1963 -- Kissinger memoranda on Senator Goldwater's announced position on nuclear weapons in Europe.
    Tab 21 Draft NAR Statement, Troop Withdrawal from Europe, November 1, 1963
    Tab 22 Position Paper, Eisenhower Statement on Troop Withdrawal, November 19, 1963 -- Kissinger prepared statement to response to former President Eisenhower's comments on NATO troops in Europe.
    Tab 23 Position Paper, NATO and European Integration, December 1963
    Tab 24 Position Paper, Withdrawal of U.S. Forces from Europe, December 1963
    Tab 25 Press Kit, NATO, January 1, 1964 -- published booklet on NAR position on NATO and European Unity.
    Tab 26 Position Paper, Authority to Use Tactical Nuclear Weapons, January 27, 1964
    Tab 27 "Manchester (N.H.) Union-Leader" Questionnaire, NATO, February 29, 1964 -- specific question about NATO posed to NAR as part of interview with the New Hampshire paper.
    Tab 28 California Republican Assembly Questionnaire, NATO, February 27, 1964 -- NAR response to question on NATO as posed by California Republican Assembly.
    Tab 29 "As A Republican, I Believe... " NATO, May 11, 1964 -- section pertaining to NATO from published brochure of NAR positions on issues affecting the United States and the Republican Party.
    Tab 30 Draft NAR Statement, NATO, May 22, 1964 -- draft of NAR speech on NATO.
    Tab 31 Platform Planks, Western Europe, May 29, 1964
    Tab 32 Platform Planks, NATO, June 3, 1964
    Tab 33 "Model" Platform, Western Europe and NATO, June 18, 1964
    Tab 34 NAR Suggestions for Platform, July 7, 1964
    Tab 35 Draft Speech, Philadelphia, October 29, 1964 -- Kissinger draft of NAR speech.
  - Volume 24 - Nuclear Testing, 1959-1964 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    Tab 1 Background Paper, The Case for Ending Nuclear Tests, summary prepared by Douglas Bailey, August 1960 -- analysis of article, "The Case for Ending Nuclear Tests" by Hans Bethe, "Atlantic Monthly," August 1960.
    Tab 2 NAR Statement, Nuclear Testing, October 27, 1961 -- press release of NAR remarks delivered at the 52nd Annual Convention of Sigma Delta Chi, Miami, Florida.
    Tab 3 Background Paper, UN Action on Nuclear Testing, November 9, 1961
    Tab 4 NAR Statement, Nuclear Testing and the Test Ban, November 14, 1961 -- press release.
    Tab 5 Background Paper, Nuclear Testing: Report No. 1 - January to November, 1961, December 7, 1961 -- Kissinger memoranda with material on nuclear testing.
    Tab 6 Position Paper, Resumption of Atmospheric Testing, February 8, 1962
    Tab 7 Position Paper, Nuclear Testing: General, April 12, 1962
    Tab 8 Position Paper, Nuclear Testing: General, April 16, 1962
    Tab 9 Position Paper, Continuation of U.S. Tests, June 22, 1962
    Tab 10 NAR Statement, Nuclear Testing and the Test Ban, August 9, 1962 -- press release.
    Tab 11 Position Paper, Nuclear Testing: General, September 28, 1962
    Tab 12 Current Positions Cards, Nuclear Testing, October 25, 1962
    Tab 13 NAR Statement, Nuclear Testing and the Test Ban, January 28, 1963 -- press release.
  - Volume 24 - Nuclear Testing, 1959-1964 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    Tab 14 Background Paper, Nuclear Testing: Two-Year Summary, March 10, 1963 -- report detailing Kennedy Administration efforts on nuclear testing issues.
    Tab 15 Background Paper, Tabular Summary of U.S. and Soviet Nuclear Test Ban Treaty Proposals, August 8, 1963 -- comparative chart outlining differences between US and USSR proposals on nuclear weapons issues.
    Tab 16 NAR Statement, Nuclear Testing and the Test Ban, August 12, 1963 -- published booklet of NAR statement given to the press at a press conference in Albany, New York.
    Tab 17 Questions and Answers prepared for "U.S. News & World Report," Nuclear Testing, September 5, 1963 and Release September 23, 1963 -- specific questions on nuclear testing posed to NAR as part of interview with the news magazine.
    Tab 18 Background Paper, Nuclear Test Ban Treaty, September 6, 1963
    Tab 19 Summary of NAR Proposals, Nuclear Testing, October 1963
    Tab 20 Background Paper, Ratification of the Test Ban Treaty, October 2, 1963
    Tab 21 Associated Press Questionnaire, Nuclear Testing, October 17, 1963
    Tab 22 Position Paper, Nuclear Testing and the Test Ban Treaty, December 1963
    Tab 23 Press Kit, Nuclear Testing, January 1, 1964 -- published booklet on NAR position on nuclear testing and the Nuclear Test Ban Treaty.
    Tab 24 Position Paper, Breaking of the Test Ban Treaty, January 8, 1964 -- NAR position on Goldwater statement to renounce US participation in the Test Ban Treaty.
    Tab 25 Background Paper, Delayed Development of Peaceful Uses of Nuclear Explosives, February 27, 1964 -- memoranda on "Project Plowshare," a plan for peaceful uses for nuclear explosives.
    Tab 26 California Republican Assembly Questionnaire, Nuclear Testing, February 27, 1964 -- NAR response to question on nuclear testing as posed by California Republican Assembly.
    Tab 27 Plowshare Fact Sheet, April 13, 1964 -- memoranda concerning Johnson administration plans to cutback on Project Plowshare.
    Tab 28 Statement for Senator Kuchel, Nuclear Testing, May 11, 1964 -- NAR responses to differences between Senator Goldwater and the 1960 Platform.
    Tab 29 Draft (#4) NAR Statement, Administration Cutback in Operation Plowshare, May 22, 1964
    Tab 30 Platform Analysis Notebook, May 1964
    Tab 31 Platform Planks, May 29, 1964 & June 4, 1964
  - Volume 25 - Southeast Asia, 1959-1964 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    Tab 1 Background Paper, Indian Political Trends, prepared by Myron Wiener, December 23, 1959 -- paper written by Professor Wiener of the University of Chicago.
    Tab 2 Background Paper, The Off-Shore Islands, prepared by T. B. Koons, November 25, 1959
    Tab 3 Background Paper, China in a 10-Year Perspective, prepared by George Taylor, March 16, 1960 -- paper written by Professor Taylor of the Chinese and Russian Institute of the University of Washington.
    Tab 4 Background Paper, Indian Economic Development in the Sixties, prepared by John P. Lewis, April 22, 1960
    Tab 5 Background Paper, American Programs in India - An Assessment, prepared by Thomas Keehn, April 1960 -- paper written by Keehn of the Indian Cooperative Union, New Delhi, India.
    Tab 6 Background Paper, Japan, prepared by Robert Scalapino, May 4, 1960
    Tab 7 Comparison of Republican and Democratic Platforms, Asian Sections, September 9, 1960 -- comparative statements of the planks on Communist China of the two parties.
    Tab 8 Background Paper, South Vietnam, February 1962
    Tab 9 Position Paper, South Vietnam - General, February 8, 1962
    Tab 10 Position Paper, Indonesia and New Guinea - General, February 8, 1962
    Tab 11 Background Paper, Republic of South Vietnam: Report No. 1 (including Summary), April 11, 1962
    Tab 12 Position Paper, South Vietnam - General, April 16, 1962
    Tab 13 Position Paper, Laos and Vietnam - General, April 16, 1962
    Tab 14 Position Paper, Laos - General, April 16, 1962
  - Volume 25 - Southeast Asia, 1959-1964 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    Tab 15 Position Paper, China[s] - General, April 16, 1962
    Tab 16 Background Paper, Laos, May 21, 1962 -- Kissinger memoranda on US policy in Laos.
    Tab 17 Draft NAR Statement, Laos, May 22, 1962
    Tab 18 Background Paper, Laos, May 28, 1962
  - Volume 26 - Southeast Asia, 1961-1964 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    Tab 19 Position Paper, Indonesia and New Guinea, June 20, 1962
    Tab 20 Position Paper, Southeast Asia - General, June 21, 1962
    Tab 21 Position Paper, Indonesia and New Guinea - General, October 1, 1962
    Tab 22 Position Paper, South Vietnam - General, October 4, 1962
    Tab 23 Position Paper, Southeast Asia - General, October 4, 1962
    Tab 24 Position Paper, Laos - General, October 10, 1962
    Tab 25 Position Paper, China - General, October 18, 1962
    Tab 26 Current Positions Cards, Southeast Asia, October 2, 1962
    Tab 27 Questions and Answers prepared for "U.S. News & World Report," Southeast Asia, September 9, 1963 -- specific questions on Southeast Asia posed to NAR as part of interview with the news magazine.
    Tab 28 Summary of NAR Proposals, Southeast Asia, October 1963
    Tab 29 Associated Press Questionnaire, Southeast Asia, October 10, 1963
    Tab 30 Questions and Answers for "Issues and Answers," Southeast Asia, October 27, 1963 -- materials prepared for NAR in advance of television appearance.
    Tab 31 Draft NAR Statement, South Vietnam, October 29, 1963 -- Kissinger memoranda on NAR position in response to White House statements issued upon return of Henry Cabot Lodge from Vietnam.
    Tab 32 Draft NAR Statement, South Vietnam, November 7, 1963
    Tab 33 Position Paper, South Vietnam, General, December 1963
    Tab 34 Position Paper, Indonesian Involvement in Malaysian Affairs, December 1963
    Tab 35 Position Paper, Communist China - General, December 1963
    Tab 36 Position Paper, U.S. Policy in Vietnam, January 1, 1964
    Tab 37 Position Paper, Admission of Communist China to the United Nations, January 1, 1964
    Tab 38 Position Paper, Admission of Communist China to the United Nations, January 8, 1964
    Tab 39 Position Paper, Neutralization of Cambodia, January 8, 1964 -- suggested NAR position on neutrality of Cambodia, as requested by the Cambodian government.
    Tab 40 Position Paper, Malaysia - General, January 13, 1964
  - Volume 26 - Southeast Asia, 1961-1964 (Box 11, Folder 62)
    Tab 41 Draft NAR Statement, South Vietnam, January 16, 1964
    Tab 42 Summary Paper, Malaysia, January 30, 1964
    Tab 43 Position Paper, Malaysian-Indonesian Crisis, January 20, 1964 -- Kissinger suggestions for NAR responses to questions on the looming crisis in Indonesia.
    Tab 44 Position Paper, Malaysian-Indonesian Crisis, January 24, 1964
    Tab 45 Position Paper, French Recognition of Communist China, January 27, 1964 -- suggested NAR response to French recognition of Communist China.
    Tab 46 NAR Statement, South Vietnam, January 28, 1964 -- press release of NAR statement delivered at a press conference in Los Angeles, California.
    Tab 47 Background Paper, Malaysia, January 29, 1964
    Tab 48 Draft NAR Statement, Malaysian-Indonesian Crisis, February 18, 1964
    Tab 49 Draft NAR Statement for Re-Issue, South Vietnam, February 19, 1964
    Tab 50 NAR Statement, South Vietnam, February 23, 1964 -- press release.
    Tab 51 "Manchester (N.H.) Union-Leader" Questionnaire, Southeast Asia, February 29, 1964 -- NAR response to question on Southeast Asia as posed by New Hampshire newspaper.
    Tab 52 Draft NAR Statement, South Vietnam, March 4, 1964
    Tab 53 Draft NAR Statement, South Vietnam, March 9, 1964
    Tab 54 Draft NAR Statement, Laos, March 26, 1964
    Tab 55 Position Paper, Military Agreement between South Vietnam and Laotian Rightists, April 3, 1964
    Tab 56 Fact Sheet, Malaysia, April 13, 1964
    Tab 57 NAR Statement, South Vietnam, April 27, 1964
    Tab 58 Fact Sheet, Laos, April 29, 1964
    Tab 59 Background Paper, The Crisis in Laos, May 5, 1964
    Tab 60 "As a Republican, I Believe... " Southeast Asia, May 11, 1964 -- section pertaining to Southeast Asia from published brochure of NAR positions on issues affecting the United States and the Republican Party.
    Tab 61 NAR Statement, Laos, May 21, 1964 -- press release of NAR statement on Laos, delivered in Fresno, California.
    Tab 62 Background Paper, Cambodian-South Vietnamese Relations, May 22, 1964
    Tab 63 Background Paper, The Crisis in Laos, May 22, 1964
    Tab 64 Background Paper, Analysis of Stevenson's U.N. Speech of May 21, 1964, May 22, 1964 -- summary of UN Ambassador Adlai Stevenson speech for possible use by NAR in a statement.
  - Volume 26 - Southeast Asia, 1961-1964 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    Tab 65 Background Paper, Malaysia, May 22, 1964
    Tab 66 Draft NAR Statement, Malaysian-Indonesian Crisis, May 22, 1964
    Tab 67 Draft NAR Statement, South Vietnam, May 23, 1964
    Tab 68 Position Paper, Goldwater Proposal to Use Low-Yield Nuclear Bombs in South Vietnam, May 25, 1964 -- Kissinger approved NAR position on Goldwater statement condoning use of nuclear weapons in Southeast Asia.
    Tab 69 NAR Statement, Malaysian-Indonesian Crisis, May 25, 1964 -- press release of NAR statement delivered at San Diego State College, San Diego, California.
    Tab 70 Draft Platform, Southeast Asia, May 29, 1964